A Guide to the Paul A. Weiss papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA124
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Manuscripts, 1940-1971; 7; 3.96 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  - Neural Development in Biological Perspective (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Neurobiology in Statu Nascendi (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Neuronal Dynamics and Axonal Flow I (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Neuronal Dynamics and Axonal Flow I (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Neuronal Dynamics and Axonal Flow III (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Neuronal Dynamics and Axonal Flow IV (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Neuronal Dynamics and Axonal Flow V (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Neuronal Dynamics (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Neuronal Uptake (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Neurospecificity (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - New Venture in Higher Education (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Organelles in Axonal Flow (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Organic Nature (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Panta Rhei (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Preface to Research and the Community (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Presidents' Science Advisory Committee (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Principles of Development (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Principles of Development (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Program for a Program (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Publications, 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Publishing Information (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Rabes, Hartmut (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Report of the Committee on Educational Policies (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Reports (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Research in Retrospect (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Research Reports (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Reviews of Weiss Publications (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Schwann Cells and Their Transformations (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Science and the Humanities (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Science in the University (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Science Looks at Itself (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Science of Life (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Science of Life (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Science of Life (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Science of Life (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Scientific Thought in the 18th Century (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Selected Papers (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Society, Stress and Security (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Some Fragments for a Canon on Educational Policy (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Structure as the Coordinating Principle in the Life of the Cell (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - System of Nature (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Taylor and Weiss (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Technical Notes (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Theoretical Distribution of 2-dimensional Projections (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Toward Unity of Culture (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - When One Plus One Does not Equal Two.... (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Whither Life Science? (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Whither Life Science? (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Within the Gates of Science and Beyond (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Wound Healing (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Theses, 1950-1960s; 8; 0.44 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes theses by students of Weiss.
  Arranged in alphabetical order by author.
  - Campbell, Richard Dana (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Dissertations of Doctoral Students (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Green, Lorna (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Robbins, Norman (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Vanable, Joseph (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Laboratory Notes, 1930-1969; 9; 1.76 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes notes and notebooks, graphs, correspondence and cell photographs.
  Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.
  - Arora and Holland Experiments, 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Assorted Laboratory Techniques (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Electron Micrographs (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Electron Microscopic Studies (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Experimental Notes, 1957-1960 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Experimental Notes, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Experimental Notes, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Experimental Record, 1928 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Experimental Record, 1957-1959 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Fernandez-Moran Study Program in the Neurosciences, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Fernandez-Moran Space for Peace Program, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Film Data (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Graphs (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Histology Notebook (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - In Vitro Synthesis (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Isotope Record Book, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory Instructions and Procedures (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Micrography Records (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Micrography Records (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Micrography Records (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Nerve Flux (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Nerve Cells (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Normal Nerves (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Notebook, 1957-1958 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Notebook 1, 1961-1965 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Notebook 2, 1961-1965 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Notebook 3, 1961-1965 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Old Notes (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Tubules (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Prints, undated; 10; 0.88 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes print album, notes, graphs, and electron microscope prints.
  Arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
  - Albums (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Data and Graphs (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Microscope Log (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Electron Microscope Notes (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Film Notes and Lists (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Fish Eggs (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Notes (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Plates and Notes (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Record of Printing (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Rotating Cell (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Professional Societies, 1946-1976; 11; 7.04 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes correspondence, photographs, notes, brochures and publications.
  Arranged in alphabetical order by organization.
  - Ad Hoc Committee on the Environment (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on the Environment (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Committee on International Organizations/Programs (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Committee on International Organizations/Programs (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - ACIOP, 1965-1966 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - ACIOP, 1965-1966 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - ACIOP, 1965-1966 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - The American Foundation (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - American Foundation Studies (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Bellagio Conference on Marine Biology (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Bioengineering (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Brussels World's Fair (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Center for Human Understanding (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - CIB A Foundation (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Club of Rome (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Club of Rome (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Club of Rome (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Club of Rome, Aurelio Peccei (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Club of Rome, Bern Conference, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Club of Rome, Cambridge, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Club of Rome, Montebello, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Club of Rome, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Club of Rome Berlin Meeting, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Club of Rome Interim Report #25, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Club of Rome Membership List (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Club of Rome Notes (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Club of Rome, Philadelphia (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Club of Rome US Chapter (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Documentation Service (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Dutch Society for Cell Biology (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Edison Foundation (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Policy Colloquium (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Frensham Group, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Frensham Group, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Frensham Group, 1970 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Frensham Group, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Frensham Group, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Goetze-Claren, Wolfgang (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Handler, Philip (NAS President) (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Harvey Society (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Health Research Council (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Institute of Laboratory Animal Resources (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Institute of Latin American Studies (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - International Aviation and Aerospace Exposition (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - International Brain Research Organization (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - International Biological Program (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - International Biological Program (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - International Biological Program (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - International Biological Stations (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - ICCB (International Center for Cell Biology), 1960 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - ICCB, 1962-1964 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - ICCB, 1962-1964 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - ICCB, 1962-1964 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - ICCB, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - ICCB Presidential Address, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - ICCB Professional Associates, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - ICCB Program, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - ICCB Program, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - ICCB Travel Grants, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - International Institute of Medical Electronics (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - International Science Writers Association (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - International Society for Cell Biology (ISCB) (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - ISCB Committee Meeting, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - ISCB Congress, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - ISCB Correspondence, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - ISCB Executive Committee Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - ISCB Executive Committee Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - ISCB Executive Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - ISCB Executive Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - ISCB Executive Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - ISCB Executive Committee, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - ISCB Funds (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - ISCB in Belgium (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - ISCB Membership (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - ISCB Membership (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - ISCB Membership Lists (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - ISCB Organization (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - ISCB Paris Correspondence (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - ISCB Subcommittee on International Film Center (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - ISCB Symposium (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - ISCB Differentiation and Immunology (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - ISCB Formation and Fate of Cell Organelles (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - ISCB The Neuron (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - ISCB Structure and Functions of Chromosomes (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - ISCB Vienna Meeting (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - ISCB, 1949 1954-1956 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - ISCB, 1957 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - ISCB, 1957-1958 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - ISCB, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - ISCB, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - ISCB, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - ISCB, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - ISCB, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - ISCB, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - ISCB, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Israel Institute for Biological Research (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - International Society for Developmental Biology (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - IUBS (International Union of Biological Scientists) Program, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - IUBS Program, 1963-1964 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - IUBS Program, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - IUBS Program, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - IUBS Program, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - IUBS US National Committee (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Jerusalem Center (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - NAS (National Academy of Sciences) Nominations (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - NAS Nominations (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - NAS Committee on IUBS (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - NAS Committee on Scientific and Technical Communication (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - NAS Correspondence, 1970s (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - NAS Correspondence, 1970s (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - NAS Correspondence, 1970s (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - NAS Constitution and Bylaws (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - NAS-Cosati (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - NAS Council Correspondence (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - NAS Council Governing Board (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - NAS Council Governing Board (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - NAS Council Meeting, 1965-1966 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - NAS Council Meeting, 1965-1966 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - NAS Division of Biology and Agriculture (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - NAS Executive Committee (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - NAS History (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - NAS Home Secretary (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - NAS International Biological Program (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - NAS International Organizations and Programs (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - NAS International Organizations and Programs (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - NAS Miscellaneous (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - NAS Miscellaneous (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - NAS Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - NAS National Academy of Engineering (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - NAS Natural Resources Committee (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - NAS Election, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - NAS News Report (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - NAS Proceedings (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - NAS Proceedings (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - NAS/NRC (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - NRC (National Research Council) (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - NRC Division of Medical Sciences (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - NRC Division of Medical Sciences (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - NRC Committee on Developmental Biology (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Oklahoma Medical Research Foundation (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Scientists (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - UNESCO (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Weizmann Institute of Science (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Article Reprints, 1922-1976; 12; 4.84 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes at least one copy of every article written and published by Weiss, either singly or with colleagues, in bound volumes. Also includes a dedication volume of articles written by colleagues, Developmental Biology, vol. 7, 1963.
  Arranged in chronological order. Complete bibliography found in box 71, folders 4 and 5.
  - Reprints in three bound volumes, 1921-1928 (Box 103)
  - Reprints in two bound volumes, 1929-1936 (Box 104)
  - Reprints in three bound volumes, 1935-1943 (Box 105)
  - Reprints, 1942-1976 (Box 106)
  - Reprints, 1945-1955 (Box 107)
  - Reprints, 1949-1958 (Box 108)
  - Reprints, 1956-1961 (Box 109)
  - Reprints, 1962-1964 (Box 110)
  - Reprints, 1963-1969 (Box 111)
  - Reprints, 1965-1972 (Box 112)
  - Reprints, 1969-1976 (Box 113)
  - Developmental Biology Vol. 7, 1963, Weiss Dedication volume (Box 113)
- Audio-visual Material, 1940-1970; 13; 1.76 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes projection slides, microscope slides, and audio recordings.
  Arranged by material type.
  Conditions Governing Access
  When requesting to view films -- please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1902).
  If the item does not have a designated AV number, please refer to the Title and the Film Number (which consists of a combination of Roman numerals and alphanumerics - example: III 14.1-6).
  - Dr. Paul A. Weiss Laboratory Films, 1; 500 films. Silent, Black white, varying lengths. Only available on original 16mm film.
    The RAC has a collection of some 500 films with minimal descriptive or technical information; most are views of chemical samples through a microscope and related laboratory processes, although there is some footage of lectures and presentations by Dr. Weiss. Original can notations include such titles as Salam Nerve Fiber, Margins of Liver and Kidney Cells, and Cleveland Lecture.
    Biographical / Historical
    Dr. Weiss was a biologist and professor who worked at the Rockefeller University for over 15 years.
    Arrangement
    Arranged as received, in original order.
    All inquires to view films require advanced notice of at least 24 hours, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Individual items, including those not available in modern formats, may be restricted from scholarly access at the discretion of RAC.
    File Plan
    I 450 W436 Fa 166 - I 450 W 436 Fe 4
    - WEISS/SERIES "A" (Box 1, Reel AV 153 - AV 212)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A" (Box 2, Reel AV 213 - AV 272)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A" (Box 3, Reel AV 273 - AV 332)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": UNIDENTIFIED (Box 1, Reel AV 333 - AV 377)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 378 - AV 410)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": PLUSK REVERSAL (Reel AV 411)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 412)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": SLIME MOLD (Reel AV 413)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": HEART (Reel AV 414)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": KIDNEY (Reel AV 415)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": CONFRONTATION (Reel AV 416)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": CONFRONTATION (CHICK LIVER AND KIDNEY) (Reel AV 417)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": CONFRONTATION (CHICK AND MOUSE LIVER) (Reel AV 418)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": NERVE (Reel AV 419)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": AGGREGATION (Reel AV 420)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": KIDNEY AGGREGATION (Reel AV 421)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": NERVE FIBER (Reel AV 422)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": NERVE CULTURES (Reel AV 423)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": KIDNEY (Reel AV 424)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 425)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": NERVE FIBER (Reel AV 426)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": NERVES VITRO (Reel AV 427)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": NERVE FIBER (Reel AV 428)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": AGGREGATION II (Reel AV 429)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": A.T.P. I (Reel AV 430)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": KIDNEY TUBES (Reel AV 431)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A": A.T.P. II (Reel AV 432)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A" (Reel AV 433 - AV 441)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A" (Box 2, Reel AV 442 - AV 455)
    - WEISS/SERIES "A" (Box 3, Reel AV 456 - AV 502)
    - WEISS, DR. PAUL (Reel AV 503)
    - SKIN (Reel AV 504)
    - CONFRONTATION (PARTS) REMOVED FROM EUROPE (Reel AV 505)
    - HOMOLOGOUS RESPONSE (PRINT POS #3) (Reel AV 506)
    - MOTILITY OF NERVE FIBER (Reel AV 507)
    - VIRUS (Reel AV 508)
    - CONFRONTATION (Reel AV 509)
    - P.H. (Reel AV 510)
    - NERVE MOVEMENT (COPY) (Reel AV 511)
    - NERVE FIBER MOTION (Reel AV 512)
    - NERVE FIBER MOVEMENT (Reel AV 513)
    - HOUSTON (Reel AV 514)
    - MIAMI (EXCERPTS) (Reel AV 515)
    - MIAMI (Reel AV 516)
    - DETROIT LECTURE (1ST PART, COPY) (Reel AV 517)
    - NERVE FIBER MOVEMENT (Reel AV 518)
    - DR. WEISS 1+1=2 (Reel AV 519)
    - MOTILITY OF NERVE FIBER (Reel AV 520)
    - NERVE #2 (NEG) (Reel AV 521)
    - NERVE #2 (Reel AV 522)
    - NERVES VITRO II (Reel AV 523)
    - HOMOLOGOUS RESPONSE: POS REEL I&II (Reel AV 524)
    - NEGATIVE NERVE I (Reel AV 525)
    - RAUDIN LECTURE (Reel AV 526)
    - IDENTIFICATION OF SILLIA (Reel AV 527)
    - B.B.C. (NEG) (Reel AV 528)
    - NERVE CORD CELLS (Reel AV 529)
    - IDENTIFICATION OF SILLIA (Reel AV 530)
    - CELL ALIGNMENT IN GROOVED MONOLAYERS (Reel AV 531)
    - IDENTIFICATION LIVER (Reel AV 532)
    - NERVE COATS (Reel AV 533)
    - NERVES VITRO II (Reel AV 534)
    - NERVE FIBERS VIVO (Reel AV 535)
    - NERVE FIBERS VIVO II (Reel AV 536)
    - SNAPPING (Reel AV 537)
    - XENOPUS WEB FIBER (Reel AV 538)
    - LOCOMOTION OF CHAOS (Reel AV 539)
    - FRUITING DICTYOSTELIUM (BONNER) (Reel AV 540)
    - DIE ENTUCKLUNG VON DICTYOSTELIUM MUCOROIDS (Reel AV 541)
    - MITOSIS OF THE NEWTON CELLS IN TISSUE CULTURES (Reel AV 542)
    - DEVELOPMENT OF THE SALAMANDER (Reel AV 543)
    - GASTRULATION-AMBLYSTOMA PUNCTATUM (Reel AV 544)
    - DEVELOPMENT OF ZEBRA FISH EGG (Reel AV 545)
    - NERVE FIBERS AND NEUROGLIA IN TISSUE CULTURE (Reel AV 546)
    - DIVIDING NORMAL ADULT RAT FIBRO BLASTS IN TISSUE CULTURE (Reel AV 547)
    - GROWTH OF CAPILLARIES AND ENDOTHELIUM FROM SUBCUTANEOUS TISSUE (Reel AV 548)
    - MUSCLE TRANSPORTATION IN THE RAT (Reel AV 549)
    - DE AFFERENTED LIMBS (Reel AV 550)
    - GENESIS OF CUTANEOUS LOCAL SIGN (NEG) (Reel AV 551)
    - GENESIS OF CUTANEOUS LOCAL SIGN (Reel AV 552)
    - AUSLOSUNG VON PLASMABEWEGUNGEN BEI RUHEZELLEN DURCH MITOCHONDRIENGITTE (Reel AV 553)
    - ENTSTEHUNG VON WIRBELN BEI WASSERSTROMUNGEN I (Reel AV 554)
    - ENTSTEHUNG VON WIRBELN BEI WASSERSTROMUNGEN (Reel AV 555)
    - DIE ENTWICKLUNG DER BERNSTEINCHNECKE SUCCINEA PUTRIS (Reel AV 556)
    - PROTOPLASMASTROMUNGEN IN PFLANZLICKEN ZELLEN (Reel AV 557)
    - ENTWICKLUNG VON PARASCARIS EQUORUM (Reel AV 558)
    - DIE ENTWICKLUNG DES SEEINGELEIS (Reel AV 559)
    - DIE ENTWICKLUNG DES MARINEN ANNELIDEN (Reel AV 560)
    - DER BEWEGUNGSAPPARAT VON BAKTERIAN UND PROTOZOEN (Reel AV 561)
    - BRUCHVORGANGIM GLAS (Reel AV 562)
    - REIFETEILUNGEN BEI DER SPERMATOGENESE DER SCHNARRHEOSCHREAKE (Reel AV 563)
    - SPANNUNGSOPTIK (Reel AV 564)
    - ACTINOSPHAERIUM EICHNORNI EHRBG (Reel AV 565)
    - SPIRALWACKSTUM DER KRISTALLO (Reel AV 566)
    - SLIME MOLD AGGREGATION (Reel AV 567)
    - CHRISTMAS LECTURE IV (Reel AV 568)
    - CHRISTMAS III (Reel AV 569)
    - BONE MARROW VI (Reel AV 570)
    - BONE MARROW V (Reel AV 571)
    - BONE MARROW IV (Reel AV 572)
    - BONE MARROW III (Reel AV 573)
    - BONE MARROW II (Reel AV 574)
    - BONE MARROW I (Reel AV 575)
    - AGGREGATION IDENTIFICATION (Reel AV 576)
    - CHICK LIVER CELLS SPREADING (Reel AV 577)
    - AGGREGATION (Reel AV 578)
    - WALLERIAN DEGENERATION (Reel AV 579)
    - 2 H LIVER CELLS (Reel AV 580)
    - P.H. ORIGINAL (Reel AV 581)
    - WEISS, DR. PAUL- PERSONAL (Reel AV 582)
    - SPIKES III (Reel AV 583)
    - SPIKES I (Reel AV 584)
    - NERVE II (Reel AV 585)
    - MOBILITY OF NERVE FIBER #1 (Reel AV 586)
    - NERVE (Reel AV 587)
    - PRESSED NERVE (Reel AV 588)
    - NERVE #1 (Reel AV 589)
    - WEISS-UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 590)
    - B.B.C.- CELLS ON GROOVES (Reel AV 591)
    - HOMOLOGOUS RESPONSE #1 (NEG) (Reel AV 592)
    - HOMOLOGOUS RESPONSE #2 (NEG) (Reel AV 593)
    - P.H., 2 CELLS, ROOT TIP, CYCLOSIS, MOUSE LUNG (Reel AV 594)
    - CELL MOVEMENT (Reel AV 595)
    - CONFRONTATION (Reel AV 596)
    - NEURAL FLOW (Reel AV 597)
    - NERVE (Reel AV 598)
    - CINETIQUE ET DEVELOPMENT D'ORGANS EMBRYONNAIRES INVETRO/DEVELOPMENT OF EMBRYONIC ORGANS (Reel AV 599)
    - CHRISTMAS LECTURE (Reel AV 600)
    - CHRISTMAS LECTURE #1 (PRINT) (Reel AV 601)
    - CHRISTMAS LECTURE #2 (PRINT) (Reel AV 602)
    - CHRISTMAS LECTURE III (Reel AV 604)
    - CONFRONTATION (Reel AV 605)
    - WEISS-UNIDENTIFIED (COPY) (Reel AV 606)
    - WEISS-UNIDENTIFIED (NEG) (Reel AV 607)
    - B.B.C. (Reel AV 608)
    - CHRISTMAS I & II ORIGINAL (Reel AV 609)
    - DETROIT (Reel AV 610)
    - CHRISTMAS (UNUSED SEQUENCES) (Reel AV 611)
    - CLEVELAND LECTURE (COPY) (Reel AV 612)
    - KENNAWAY LECTURE (Reel AV 613)
    - CONFRONTATION (Reel AV 614)
    - CONFRONTATION II (Reel AV 615)
    - MYPTIC (HOMOLOGOUS) FUNCTION (Reel AV 616)
    - FORTPFLANZUNG DER FORAMINIFEREN (LICHTTONKOPIE) (Reel AV 617)
    - BACILLUS CIRCULANS-AUFBAU UND VERHALTEN BEWEGLICHER KOLONIEN (Reel AV 618)
    - USIA SCIENCE (Reel AV 619)
    - ENTWICKLUNG VON DICTYOSELIUM - LICHTTON (Reel AV 620)
    - MICROPUNCTURE OF CELLS BY UV MICROBEAM (BESSIS) (Reel AV 621)
    - WEISS-UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 622)
    - CHRISTMAS LECTURE II (Reel AV 623)
    - CHRISTMAS LECTURE III (Reel AV 624)
    - WEISS-UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 625)
    - CONFRONTATION (Reel AV 626)
    - PROMISE OF THE LIFE SCIENCES: FINE STRUCTURE AND PATTERN OF LIVING THINGS, REEL I (by Paul Weiss) (Reel AV 627)
    - PROMISE OF THE LIFE SCIENCES: FINE STRUCTURE AND PATTERN OF LIVING THINGS, REEL II (by Paul Weiss) (Reel AV 628)
    - CRAIG, DR. LYMAN #1 (Reel AV 629)
    - CRAIG, DR. LYMAN #2 (CELLS COLOR?) (Reel AV 630)
    - CRAIG, DR. LYMAN #3 (Reel AV 631)
    - CRAIG, DR. LYMAN #4 (Reel AV 632)
    - HOMOLOGOUS RESPONSE (SOME ORIGINAL POSITIVE OF SALAMANDER & FROG) (Reel AV 633)
    - UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 634)
    - PH AND MITOCHONDRIA (Reel AV 635)
    - MICROSPIKES A.T.D. (Reel AV 636)
    - UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 637)
    - UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 638)
    - UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 639)
    - CONFRONTATION (REMOVED) (Reel AV 640)
    - BIOPHYSICS (Reel AV 641)
    - DR. GEORGE WEISS (Reel AV 642)
    - TRECHEAL EPITHELIUM ON EDGE (COPY) (Reel AV 643)
    - WOUND HEALING (Reel AV 644)
    - ZOOM FILM (PERFECT PRINT) (Reel AV 645)
    - UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 646)
    - ZOOM (FROM MACROSCOPIC TO MACROMOLECULAR DIMENSIONS) (Reel AV 647)
    - MARGINS OF LIVER AND KIDNEY CELLS (Reel AV 648)
    - CHRISTMAS LECTURE IV (NEG) (Reel AV 649)
    - CELL FILM (Reel AV 650)
    - ZOOM (Reel AV 651)
    - SALAM NERVE FIBER (Reel AV 652)
    - HOMOLOGOUS RESPONSE (Reel AV 653)
    - 2 CENTER (Reel AV 654)
    - PLUSK REMOVED (Reel AV 655)
    - MONOLAYER GROOVES (Reel AV 656)
    - SLIME MOLD (Reel AV 657)
    - UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 658)
    - UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 659)
    - UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 660)
    - (TAIL END OF) NERVE DEMONSTRATION (Reel AV 661)
    - NERVE MOVEMENT I (Reel AV 662)
    - NERVE MOVEMENT II (Reel AV 663)
    - NERVE FIBERS (BURNED) (Reel AV 664)
    - WEISS-UNIDENTIFIED (Reel AV 665)
    - NERVE MITOCHONDRIA (Reel AV 666)
    - REVERSIBLE SWELLING OF MITOCHONDRIA (Reel AV 667)